let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " What is the purpose of Bootstrap in web development?",
    answer: "To design responsive and mobile-first websites",
    options: [
      "To create server-side scripts",
      
      "To enhance database performance",
      
      "To design responsive and mobile-first websites",
      "To optimize SEO techniques"
      
      
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which class is used in Bootstrap to create a responsive, mobile-friendly grid system?",
    answer: ".col-md",
    options: [
      ".row",
      ".col-md",
      ".container",
      ".navbar"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which Bootstrap component is used for navigation purposes?",
    answer: ".navbar",
    options: [
      ".tab",
      ".navbar",
      
      ".nav",
      ".nav-item"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " Which class is used in Bootstrap to create a full-width container that spans the entire width of the viewport?",
    
    answer: ".container-fluid",
    options: [
        ".container" ,
       ".container-fluid" ,
       ".row" ,  
      ".col-lg" 
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which class is used to create a button in Bootstrap?",
    answer: ".btn",
    options: [
      ".btn",
      ".btn-primary",
      ".button-style",
      ".button"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb:6,
    question:" Which class is used in Bootstrap to hide an element visually but keep it accessible for screen readers?",
    answer:".sr-only",
    options:[
        ".hidden",
        ".hide",
        ".sr-only",
        ".invisible"
        
    ]
  },

  {
    numb:7,
    question:"Which class is used to create a responsive table in Bootstrap? ",
    
    answer:".table-responsive",
    options:[
        ".responsive-table",
        ".table-fluid",
        ".table-responsive-sm",
        ".table-responsive"
        
        
    ]
  },

  {
    numb:8,
    question:"Which utility class in Bootstrap is used to add spacing to an element?",
    answer:".margin",
    options:[
        ".space",
        ".margin",
        ".spacing",
        ".padding"
        
    ]
  },

  {
    numb:9,
    question:" In Bootstrap, which class is used to create a responsive image that scales with the size of the parent element?",
    answer:".img-fluid",
    options:[
        ".img-responsive",
        ".responsive-img",
        ".image-scale",
        ".img-fluid"
        
        
        
    ]
  },

  {
    numb:10,
    question:"Which class in Bootstrap is used to align text to the center?",
    
    answer:".text-center",
    options:[
        ".center-text",
        ".align-center",
        ".text-center",
        ".center-align"
        
        
    ]
  },
  
];